admissionjankari.com 2013-06-09

# Privacy Policy - Admission Jankari

##  Privacy Policy 

**Introduction**

AddmissionJankari.com is one of the web products of [Iry Tech Pvt. Ltd.](http://irytech.com/) enabling users to create personal web profiles. We respect the privacy of the users and are committed to protect it in all respects. If you have any query related to the privacy policy, please email us at **[privacypolicy@admissionjankari.com.](mailto:privacypolicy@admissionjankari.com.)**

To avail certain sites / services on our websites, users are required to provide certain information for the registration process namely:- a) your name, b) email address, c) sex, d) age, e) PIN code etc., and / or interests, and the like. (All required information is Service Dependent). The Information as supplied by the users enables us to serve their needs in a more meaningful manner and, also to authenticate users and send periodic notifications to the users willing to receive our newsletters and updates. Users may choose not to receive email of this type by changing their "notification" setting to "Do not send me notification emails" in the user "Account Settings". To keep the track of hits and security perspective, admissionjankari.com also logs IP address and browser type. AdmissionJankari.com promises that we will not sell or rent your personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes without your explicit consent. From time to time, we may reveal general statistical information about our Web site and visitors, such as the number of visitors, services purchased, etc. Your trust and confidence are our highest priority. 

To improve the responsiveness of the sites for our users, we may use "cookies", or similar electronic tools to collect information to assign each visitor a unique random number as a User Identification (User ID) to understand the user's individual interests using the Identified Computer. Unless you voluntarily identify yourself (through registration, for example), we will have no way of knowing who you are, even if we assign a cookie to your computer. The only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply. A cookie cannot read data of your hard drive. Our advertisers may also assign their own cookies to your browser (if you click on their ads), a process that we do not control. 

AdmissionJankari.com contains links to sites and we are not responsible for the privacy policies and practices on other sites. When linking to another site a user should read the privacy policy stated on that site.

**Disclaimer & Legal Requests**

There are stages where user needs to use their credit card to avail certain features available exclusively on paid method. Please be noted that once a credit card transaction or any transaction for that matter has been completed, all card data is moved off-line only to ensure that the data/credit card information received is not accessible to anyone after completion of the on-line transaction and to ensure the maximum security. We take utmost care to ensure the security of any nature of electronic transaction. AdmissionJankari.com shall not be liable for any loss or damage sustained by reason of any disclosure (inadvertent or otherwise) of any information concerning the user's account and / or information relating to or regarding online transactions using credit cards / debit cards and / or their verification process and particulars nor for any error, omission or inaccuracy with respect to any information so disclosed and used whether or not in pursuance of a legal process or otherwise. 

We cooperate with law enforcement and regulatory inquiries, as well as other third parties to enforce laws, such as: intellectual property rights, fraud and other rights, to help protect you and the community from malicious people. Therefore, in response to a verified request by law enforcement or other government officials relating to a criminal investigation or alleged illegal activity, we can (and you authorize us to) disclose your name, city, state, telephone number, email address, User ID history. Without limiting the above, in an effort to respect your privacy and our ability to keep the community free from bad actors, we will not otherwise disclose your personal information to law enforcement or other government officials without a legal reason, court order or substantially similar legal procedure, except when we believe in good faith that the disclosure of information is necessary to prevent imminent physical harm or financial loss; or report suspected illegal activity. Further, we can (and you authorize us to) disclose your name, address, city, state, country, phone number, email, and company name to Intellectual Property rights owners under confidentiality agreement, as we in our sole discretion believe necessary or appropriate in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringement, piracy, or other unlawful activity.

**Changes in Privacy Policy**

[Iry Tech Pvt. Ltd.](http://irytech.com/) reserves the right to amend the Privacy Policy and the updated policy will be displayed on the AdmissionJankari.com site as and when changed for public viewing.

Tell us what you ‘Think’ AdmissionJankari.com welcomes your questions and comments regarding our privacy policy. You may contact us at **[info@admissionjankari.com.](mailto:info@admissionjankari.com.)**

* * *
